Jon! And. uh...
Hi. Mom. Hi. Dad.
I'm Lara.
We... we have a daughter?
Lara...
And Jon. you're back!
It's Jonathan.
And what do you mean I'm back?
I've never been here before in my life.
You were here a month ago.
We saved your father. remember?
What are they talking about. Lara?
I... don't know.
What?
He doesn't remember me.
So. when we changed the future. uh...
We rewrote Jon's entire life.
You know. most people prepare
for a Pentagon inspection.
That's a rather... severe look.
even for you.
Care to catch me up
on your little science project?
It's on a need-to-know-basis.
and you don't need to know.
We're supposed to be partners. remember?
No. Wilson. you work for me. remember?
Hello. Lex.
Uh. Director Waller. you're...
Yes. back in charge.
I guess you work for her now.
So we've already done this?
Just you. Lara wasn't here.
But we're so happy to meet you.
Wait. I didn't exist?
Not technically.
Was I. like. an accident?
Uh...
look. look. look.
If... if things didn't
work out last time...
-They did.
-You saved me.
Stop saying that!
That wasn't me.
It was you. A version of you.
And you coming back
made everything better.
Then why is my future worse?
Beautiful day out. eh?
The weather is pleasant.
So where are we now. Kara?
The sky. over Metropolis.
Headed to Smallville.
No. no. I-I mean. where are we...
with each other?
Are you... I mean. am I...
Hey. did I say something wrong up there?
Jimmy Flamebird.
what do you want?
Uh. I guess I-I-I'd wanna be
a better friend. Kara.
I see. A friend.
Is that all you want?
I-I just wanna be with you.
What do you want?
I want to trust you...
but I am afraid
you will leave me alone again.
Kara. I...
Oh good. you're here.
Kara. Jimmy. this is Lara and Jonathan.
From the future...
again.
Jon. you're back.
He's not that Jon.
He's... new.
Yes.
Do not provoke him.
Understood.
Welcome. new Jon.
It's... Jonathan.
Hey. we should get back on mission.
'Cause that worked out so well
for the last guy.
Uh. what mission?
The mission General Lane gave us.
Wow. Dad just can't stop giving orders.
Well. whatever got you here.
I'm glad to have Superboy back.
Don't call me Superboy.
I'm Superman.
Uh. we already have a Superman.
Do you?
Superman this. Superboy that.
Who wants a super slice
of Pa Kent's world famous...
I'm done with this.
Or there's snickerdoodles.
Jonathan.
I... I know all of this
must be strange for you.
But if you need to talk...
I'm here to listen.
You think we can just
have a heart to heart?
Maybe give me a motivational speech.
promise me a better tomorrow?
You... you think. what.
we're just gonna play catch?
I learned to use my powers
on my own. okay?
I defended the Earth on my own.
Because you weren't there.
No one was there.
I'm not here for you this time. Superman.
Stay out of my way.
Jonathan. wait!
Ah. this again. No.
Stop!
You should try that.
Pa Kent. whoo!
That man can bake.
Hey. don't worry about Jon...
and time loops. okay?
Just tell me why you
and your brother are here.
Our mission is confidential.
Of course it is.
But General Lane sent us back
in time to kill Lex Luthor.
What?
You traveled back in time
to commit murder?
We're here to protect the future.
What kind of future do you come from?
In our time. Luthor commands
a personal army
of mind-controlled Kryptonian clones.
The Eradicators.
There has to be another way to stop him.
You don't have to kill Lex
just because my dad told you to.
Your dad?
Yeah. General Lane.
-That's not who...
-Salt and pepper crewcut.
always giving orders.
No. You told us to kill Lex Luthor.
You're General Lane.
As you can see. Lexcorp
is paving the way to a safer.
more secure Metropolis with...
Save it. Luthor.
Wilson. you're still here.
My apologies. Mr. Luthor.
But why don't you show Director Waller
your latest project?
Ah...
It's still in its infancy.
not ready for review.
-But over here...
-I insist.
Very well.
Director Waller. allow me to present...
Project Eradicator.
Once complete. this weapon
will put humanity back on top
as the world's dominant species.
Created from Superman's own living tissue.
Eradicator self-repairs. self-evolves.
and will function under my
complete direct mental control.
Mental control?
The hardware is not finished.
but once it is.
the Luthor gray matter
I put in Eradicator's brain
will let me control him with mine.
You put a piece of your brain
inside that thing?
That's all I need to see.
Shut it down. Luthor.
Wait. you don't understand.
The Eradicator will revolutionize...
No. you don't understand.
I'm not just shutting down
Project Eradicator.
I'm shutting down all of Lexcorp.
effective immediately.
Welp. I'm a horrible parent.
Me too.
Poor Jonathan.
Jonathan? I'm talking about Lara.
Ugh. you think you're doing
your best as a mother. but...
Well. at least you were there.
I somehow missed our kids' lives
two times in a row.
Maybe that's it.
Maybe I'm the problem.
I'm the reason Lara turned out this way.
Wait. what's wrong with Lara?
Wait.
Where is Lara?
Director Waller.
I... I'm...
I'm working for the good
of humankind here.
Out of my way. Luthor.
You see this?
That's a prototype time travel device.
Imagine what we could do
once it's complete.
You... you'll... you'll be able
to go back to the past
and stop your enemies
before they even strike.
I've made my decision. Luthor.
Listen. I've seen what's out there.
Superman's not even the worst of it.
There are things waiting in space that...
Superman put his life on the line
when we needed him.
I'll take space aliens over you any day.
You've not only failed
to live up to Checkmate's expectations.
you don't even look after your own.
You.
And who is this young lady?
I'm here for Luthor.
No. stop. stop! I'm... I'm... I'm...
I'm just a scientist.
Just a scientist?
You're the end of the world.
Just like Lara
to rush headlong into things.
Always trying to be mommy's
perfect little soldier.
Sorry. kids.
Whole site's locked down.
No one gets past me...
especially Kryptonians.
Where's Lara?
Lara? Is that the super-powered
teenager who tried to kill Lex?
They took the fight underground.
Who's they?
You okay. Smallville?
Yeah. the sewage broke my fall.
Oh. good.
Is Lara down here?
She must be. And the sooner we find her.
the sooner we can get out of here.
Lara?
For a second. I thought
there was a monster down here...
Shh! There is a monster down here.
Kal-El? Lois?
Let's split up. We'll find them
faster that way.
That is unwise. Jonathan.
The lead in this facility
is disrupting the...
Whatever. I don't need your permission.
Kal-El. Lois Lane. can you hear me?
Jonathan?
-Help!
No. no. no. no. no!
Jonathan!
Lara. wait.
Which way?
I-I-I think she went...
Where's my brother?
Lara!
What is that thing?
It's an Eradicator.
But... this one is different.
Back off!
Lara. you're hurt. Get back!
Don't listen to her. Get behind him.
Lara. listen to me.
No!
Stay away from my family.
Kids. wait!
Our children... are so disrespectful.
Come on. this way.
Bring your monster to heel. Luthor.
I... I... I can't stop it.
Don't you two share a brain?
What happened to "direct mental control?"
I already told you.
the system is incomplete.
It won't respond to my commands.
Eradicator's in control.
Lara!
Lara! Lara!
I am your opponent.
He's evolving too fast for us.
We've... we've lost.
Just like that other Jonathan.
There's... there's nothing we can do.
Ow!
You are not the only one
who has seen a different world. Jonathan.
I have seen other futures.
We can still choose a better tomorrow.
Stay here.
I'll show you.
She's alone with that thing.
Clark. you can't.
That's a job...
for Superman.
No.
Kara! Kara.
Why?
You...
are my better tomorrow.
Kara!
Jonathan!
What?
Not again.
My family needs me.
They need me.
Enough of this.
You... lose.
Kara!
Kara. please!
I am... too late.
She's not...
She's not waking up.
Jonathan...
Are you okay?
I couldn't stop it.
Eradicator is loose in the time stream.
So. who am I arresting?
What?
We haven't been properly introduced.
Amanda Waller. Pentagon.
Director Waller. the kids
were just following orders.
They were sent here from the future
to stop Lex from unleashing that monster.
Uh... I was defending myself
from an assassination.
The prototype was never meant
to be active at this stage.
It... it's her fault.
That... that... that...
Slade. you tell them.
You saw everything.
You know what I was trying to accomplish.
What we were trying to do.
I tried to tell you. Alex.
Wilson...
book Lex Luthor.
We'll sort out our... new guests later.
What are we gonna do. Clark?
Kara.
the kids.
the monster...
How are we gonna fix this?
I... I think I know where my powers are.
I think I can get them back.
You can bring back Superman?
I think so. but I...
I'll have to leave.
For a little while.
Clark. no.
No. you can't leave me alone
with these kids.
I'll fail them. We know I fail them.
You aren't the person
who sent them here. Lois.
They need the real you.
This you.
But I need you. Clark.
Our whole future is getting ripped away.
First Jon and now...
I'm only going away for a little while.
We can't save the kids.
We... we can't save the future...
without Superman.
Promise me. then.
Promise me. Clark. that you'll come back.
I promise.